(Raj:)Does the smart-ass know
that Terminator was actually
(Raj:)ripped off from an Outer Limits
script called
(Raj:)Demon With a Glass Hand,
by Harlan Ellison?
(Leonard:)Oh, does the gazelle know that
according to Harlan Ellison,
(Leonard:)it was not ripped off
from Demon With a Glass Hand,
(Leonard:)but was ripped off from another
Outer Limits script
(Leonard:)he wrote called The Soldier?
(Penny:)I'm gonna need another clue.
(Howard:)Okay, give me the flowers and pie.
(Sheldon:)But if we show up
and you're holding them,
(Sheldon:)she'll think they're only from you.
(Howard:)They are only from me.
(Howard:)You said the gift of you was enough.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but now that I've seen
what the gift of me
(Sheldon:)with flowers and pie looks like,
there's no going back.
(Sheldon:)Boy, I can't wait to see
the look on her face...
(Sheldon:)We're leaving right now.
(Howard:)-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
Sheldon, tell me what's going on!
(Sheldon:)I saw my mommy with a naked man
(Sheldon:)and she was trying
to be a mommy again.